Rich people like you
must have lost all your worries long ago.
I don't have worries.
I only have annoyance right now.
Because of Yue Shanchuan?
What exactly do you like about him?
His face and body.
There are plenty of handsome guys
with good faces and bodies.
Why get hung up on just one?
But he's different.
Sometimes,
I feel like
he's an unyielding bamboo.
But then he inadvertently reveals
a hint of softness.
Don't you think
he's especially cute
when he's all serious yet
looking so miserable and bitter?
Don't laugh. Don't you think so?
I think...
falling for
a broke, broken,
and miserable little puppy
is the destiny of rich people like you.
I've finally figured it out.
But I'm sure he's into me.
Even though I haven't known
Yue Shanchuan for long,
I feel like
he takes relationships very seriously.
If he won't accept you,
it must be because he can't handle
the gap between you two.
He's afraid he can't treat you
well enough or take responsibility.
I don't need him to take responsibility.
The gap between us is unavoidable.
If he were smart,
he'd seize the opportunity to climb up
while I still like him.
Then let me ask you,
if he did that,
how would he be any different
from Yue Yingying?
You wouldn't have fallen for him, either.
That's true.
Think about it.
Yun.
Excuse me, who is this?
It hasn't been that long since you quit.
Have you forgotten your Mr. Hu?
Hu the dog... No, no, no, Mr. Hu.
I heard you opened a B&B
after leaving the company.
We all saw your ads.
Our department is having
a team building event these two days.
Can you arrange it at your place?
My place is really too small
to host you, Mr. Hu.
I know.
Your little place
doesn't meet the company's
team building standards.
But as your former boss,
I definitely need to support you.
No, Mr. Hu,
my place is really...
No need to thank me too much.
We're here. Open the door.
Look, a swimming pool.
Not bad, not bad.
It's worth the trip.
Hurry up.
Great, great.
Yun, you've done a good job here.
You truly are my protégé.
Doing great wherever you go.
By the way, is your promotion still on?
Sorry,
the promotion is over.
Yun,
don't be so rigid.
It makes no sense to turn away
customers,
right?
You're a veteran of the company.
You know our department's
team-building budget.
How about this?
I'll make the call
and give you the entire budget.
We'll just hang out here for three days.
Just get us three rooms.
You can keep
the extra money.
Consider it my support for your startup.
Thank you for your kindness, Mr. Hu.
But your budget
isn't enough to cover
three rooms for three days.
I'm just an employee.
I don't call the shots,
and I can't explain it to my boss.
How about this?
Book a discounted room
for the two of them.
They're girls.
A big room might scare them.
Besides, it's pretty cool
in the mountains.
A window doesn't really matter.
Mr. Hu, Yun,
Same old problem.
You only say no when facing issues.
You need to find a way to solve them.
You won't accomplish anything
anywhere like this.
Where are your waiters?
Are you the only one here?
Waiter!
Who says there are no waiters?
I am the waiter.
So blind.
We've been here a while.
You didn't even come
help with the luggage.
Hurry up
and take it upstairs for us.
What are you waiting for?
An invitation? Hurry up.
Not bad,
really not bad.
Let's go check out the pool.
Tell you what,
let me show you to your room.
Okay.
It's fine. We can carry it ourselves.
I don't care.
Right here.
Qingqing, did you open the wrong room?
No.
Some people would do anything
to save money,
but we don't have
discount rooms at Yunbian.
We can't let you lose money.
We'll make up the difference.
Yeah, it's not easy
for you to start a business.
We can't take advantage of you.
No need.
It's not peak season anyway.
The room is empty,
so just stay here.
You must be exhausted
from the long ride.
Get some rest first.
Let me know if you need anything.
Don't let those two know,
or Mr. Hu will complain again.
Got it. If he can't take advantage,
he feels like he's losing out.
I'll get going then.
Bye.
Who's that guy?
Acting like he owns the place.
He was my direct supervisor
at my old company.
He loves bossing junior staff around
and throwing his weight around.
But thanks for bailing me out today.
If he knew I was a one-woman show,
he'd laugh his head off.
I wasn't bailing you out.
I really want to be a waitress at Yunbian.
I've thought it through.
If Yue Shanchuan won't come to my world,
I'll go check out his.
I want to see
what's so different about it.
Are you serious?
Do you have any normal clothes
I can borrow?
You have a whole closet of clothes,
yet you still want to borrow from me?
No, my clothes are all too expensive.
Yue Shanchuan definitely won't buy it.
I still need to borrow
a couple of ordinary ones from you
to keep up appearances.
I can't believe
I still couldn't escape that menace
after coming to Xinchang.
He has no other skills
but sucking up and making empty promises.
He takes all the credit
and makes me take the blame
for all the mistakes.
He brags to the bosses
all day long,
and then turns around and exploits us
to clean up his mess.
It's just the bitter tears
of a corporate slave.
He fired me just to make room
for his niece, Hu Yuqian.
But I feel like this girl
isn't the same kind of person as him.
Can you handle it alone?
Do you need my help?
I'm fine.
Different strokes for different folks.
I know that scumbag Hu's tricks
like the back of my hand.
Don't worry, I can counter them.
Okay, just call me anytime if you need me.
Or you can ask Shanchuan if he has time
for a part-time job lately.
Speaking of your buddy Yue Shanchuan,
he's really an incubus reincarnated.
He's got our Shurong completely bewitched.
She gave up being a proper lady
just to suffer for love.
She said she's packing her bags tonight
to move into Yue Shanchuan's rental.
Shanchuan isn't that kind of casual guy.
If Shurong just wants
to play around with him,
he'll never agree.
I advise Shurong
to give up on that idea.
Not necessarily.
Our Ms. Shu has the looks
and the figure.
Even a saint's heart
would skip a beat.
Alright, let's make a bet today.
Let's bet on whether Shurong
can successfully get into
Shanchuan's rental.
How about it?
What are the stakes?
If you win,
I'll give you a shard.
And if I lose?
If you lose,
give me a kiss.
I treat you with sincerity,
and you play mind games with me?
Stingy.
If you lose,
cook me a meal.
Is that okay?
If I win,
one shard isn't enough. I want ten.
Deal. Let's wait and see.
Tangbao, let's go.
Tangbao, time to go home.
Going home!
Did you work overtime today?
Why are you just coming out?
What are you doing here?
Seeking refuge with you.
Didn't I ruin
my dad and Yue Yingying's affair?
He went back and
made up some nonsense,
making my mom freeze all my cards.
I don't have a single penny
on me right now.
I can't even afford to stay
at Yunbian anymore.
If you don't take me in,
I might have to sleep
on the streets tonight.
Still no.
If it weren't for your sister,
I wouldn't be so miserable.
You have to pay for what she did.
Sorry.
It's really not convenient at my place.
No.
Little girl,
what are you doing here all alone?
It's late. It's dangerous not to go home.
Let me take you home.
What are you doing? Don't touch me.
Still shy, huh? It's okay.
I'll take you home.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Get lost.
Let's go home.
It's so stuffy after taking a shower.
The AC isn't cooling very well.
I'll turn on the fan.
It'll be cooler.
What are you doing?
Aren't we sleeping together?
I'll just sleep on the floor.
It's not like
we haven't slept together before.
Go to sleep.
It's getting late.
How can you sleep
on a bamboo mat in silk clothes?
Take them off.
What are you doing?